你们看，是乔伊的照片
Oh,look! There's Joey's picture!
真是令人兴奋
This is so exciting!
你总是能看见 从未在自己作品中出现的某人
You can spot someone who's never seen his plays.
注意力强，无畏无惧
Notice,no fear. No sense of impending doom.
"三号男演员不能让维克.夏皮罗演"
"The role of man number three will not be played by Vic Shapiro. "
看来我们来错时间了啊.
We came on the wrong night.
不敢相信我居然把杂志忘了
I can't believe I forgot a magazine.
-这样也许更好一些 -我不知道
-Come on,this might be good. -I don't know.
标题上的惊叹号让我害怕 这不只是弗洛伊德,而是弗洛伊德!
The exclamation point scares me. It's not just Freud,it's Freud!
奇迹就要出现
Magic is about to happen!
伊娃
Well,Eva...
你今天的表现不错
...we've done some excellent work here.
我得说……
And I would have to say...
……你的问题相当清楚
...your problem is quite clear.
你只是想要一个风铃
All you want is a tinkle
你讨厌流行的东西
What you envy's a schwang
听它发出清脆的声音
A thing through which you can tinkle
拨弄着它，或是挂在那边
To play with or simply let hang
六人行 第1季 第06集 屁股
The One With the Butt
丹尼尔・E・汉克出品  新音乐剧《弗洛伊德》
我感觉自己受到冒犯了
I feel violated.
还有谁感觉想剥他们的皮
Did anybody else feel like peeling their skin off...
或者做点其他的事情?
...to have something else to do?
罗斯，十点钟
Ross,10:00.
是吗?感觉像是两点
Is it? It feels like 2.
-不，十点钟 -什么?
-No,10:00! -What?
一位美女在8，9，10点钟方向
There's a beautiful woman at 8,9,10:00!
喂!
Hello!
她太美了 她让我的梦中情人变得有如矮胖的秃子
She's amazing! She makes the women l dream about look like fat,bald men.
过去啊，她旁边没人
Go over. She's not with anyone.
对，我该用什么开场白? 打扰了,啦啦啦啦之类的
And what would my opening line be? Excuse me....
拜托，她只是个人，你可以的
Come on,she's a person. You can do it.
请告诉我，我配得上她吗? 罗斯，做我的后盾吧
Could she be more out of my league? Back me up.
他这副德行一百万年都别想得到这种美女
He couldn't get a woman like that in a million years.
但这种美女,身边总是跟着蹩脚货
You always see these beautiful women with "nothing" guys.
你也可以成为其中之一
You could be one of those guys.
-没错，你能办到 -你也认为?
-You could do that. -You think?
是的.
Absolutely!
没想到我竟有这种念头
I can't believe I'm considering this.
-我一向谨言慎行 -快去
-l' m very aware of my tongue. -Come on.
我上了
Here goes.
退后，伙计.炮火来袭.
Stand back,everyone. Incoming ego shrapnel.
好的，我能做到的
All right,I can do this.
-怎么? -嗨.
-Yes? -Hi.
下个字是…
Okay,next word would be...
…钱德
... Chandler.
我叫钱德
Chandler is my name and....
嗨
Hi!
我知道，你说过
Yes,you said that.
对，我说过 但我没说我想说...
Yes! Yes,I did. But what I didn't say....
我想说的是……
What I wanted to say was...
……愿意与我约会吗? 谢谢，晚安
...would you like to go out with me? Thank you. Good night.
钱德
Chandler?
-想不到你会跳舞 -你演戏了
-I didn't know you could dance! -You were in a play!
感觉如何?
What'd you think?
-想不到你会跳舞 -你演戏了
-I didn't know you could dance! -You were in a play!
拜托，没那么糟吧 我是主角
It wasn't that bad. I was the lead.
这次我在轮唱中出现 至少你们可以看见我的头
It was better than the troll thing. At least you got to see my head.
-对没错 -我们有看见你的头
-You're right. -We saw your head.
这德国口音怎么样?
How about that accent?
不错，你的W全变成V了
Yeah. All of your W's were V's.
她答应了…
She said yes!
好烂的戏，伙计，烂
Awful play,man!
她叫亚萝拉，来自意大利 她叫我“钱德呃呃呃”
Her name's Aurora. She's ltalian and she pronounces my name " Chandler. "
我喜欢她这样称呼我
I like that better.
领座员要我把它交给你
The usher gave me this.
-这是什么? -艾斯黛雷纳德经纪公司
-What is it? -The Estelle Leonard T alent Agency.
经纪公司拿名片给我 或许他们想和我签约
An agency left its card. They wanna sign me!
因为这场戏?
Based on this play?
因为这一场戏！
Based on this play!
瞧!背面有字
Look! There's a note on the back.
"喜欢你的工作.请叫我挖墙脚的"
"Loved your work. Call me a sap. "
显然她非常的动人
She was obviously very moved!
你应该马上打电话给她
You should call her fairly quickly.
越快越好
Yeah! As soon as possible!
请进
Come in!
嗨，我来找艾斯黛雷纳德的.
Hi. I'm here to see Estelle Leonard.
等等，让我看看她在不在……
Just a moment,let me see if she's in.
你好.
Hello.
-你是艾斯黛? -我知道……
-You' re Estelle? -I know...
……你在期待 一位美丽动人的小姐.
...you weren't expecting someone so fantastically beautiful.
笨小伙.放下负担 亲爱的,坐下来
Love lump. T ake a load off already,darling. Sit already.
我无法用语言表述 到这里来我有多么兴奋
I can't tell you how excited I am to be here.
为什么?
Why not?
-我的意思是说 -你不介意我边吃边听吧
-What I meant was -You don't mind if I eat,do you?
乔伊
Joey...
……让我问你一个问题
...sweetheart,let me ask you a question.
你看过"西雅图未眠夜"这部电影吗?
Did you ever see the movie Sleepless in Seattle?
-喔!你要我扮演那些演员 -不是.
-Wow! Do you represent those actors? -No.
你知道结尾的，最后他们快乐的在一起
But you know the end,where they' re happy?
那将是你和我的结局
That's gonna be you and me.
你是说你准备和我签约
You mean you wanna sign me?
不，我要到帝国大厦顶楼去亲热.
No,I wanna go to the top of the Empire State Building and make out.
我当然是要签你啊!
Of course I wanna sign you!
小姐,我实在是 -噢,小伙子
-Miss Leonard,I'm so -Oh,boy.
-坐在那里,牛仔.  -对不起!
-Ride them,cowboy. -l' m sorry!
三维立体画
我看不到
I don't see it!
-试着穿透过去  -让你的眼睛离焦.
-T ry to look through it. -Unfocus your eyes.
集中?没有什么东西可以集中眼力
Focus? There's nothing to focus on.
-是自由女神 -对啦
-It's the Statue of Liberty! -Right!
-自由女神在哪里? -那里.
-Where's the Statue of Liberty? -There.
现在我看不到了
I can't not see it now.
嗨，小子!
Hey,kids!
到这里来.你在这里看到什么了吗?
Come here. Do you see anything here?
-看起来像一只船 -一只船.
-lt looks like a boat. -A boat.
正好在自由女神前面
Right in front of the Statue of Liberty.
我坐在这儿都七秒钟了 竟没人问我的约会如何?
It's been seven seconds,and you haven't asked me how my date went.
你的约会如何，钱德呃呃呃?
How was your date,Chandler?
真是令人难以置信
It was unbelievable!
我没见过像她那样的人 她的生活真是太令人称羡了
I've never met anyone like her. She's had an amazing life!
她穿过以色列阵地
She was in the Israeli army.
幸好子弹没打中引擎 我们才能越过边界
None of the bullets hit the engine,so we made it to the border.
真是有惊无险
But just barely,and l....
我整晚都在谈我自己，抱歉
I've been talking about myself all night long. I'm sorry.
你呢?说来听听嘛
What about you? T ell me a story.
有一回...
All right,once...
我搭地铁
... I got on the subway.
是在晚上
And it was at night...
...那晚我搭地铁到布鲁克林区
...and I rode it all the way to Brooklyn.
仅为了无聊
Just for the hell of it.
我们一直谈到两点,那真是个美好的夜晚
We talked until 2:00. It was perfect.
可以这么说
More or less.
突然我们发现自己身在也门
Suddenly,we realized we were in Yemen.
我们,我们是谁?
I' m sorry,so "we" is...?
我和瑞克
"We" is me and Rick.
瑞克是谁?
Who's Rick?
我丈夫
My husband.
-这么说你们已经离婚 -没有
-Oh,so you' re divorced? -No.
对不起，这么说你是寡妇? 希望如此
I' m sorry. So you' re widowed? Hopefully?
不，我们还是夫妻
No,l' m still married.
告诉我你丈夫做何感想? 你坐在我身旁...
So,how would your husband feel about you sitting here with me...
...脚伸到我大腿 足以数我口袋里的零钱?
...sliding your foot so far up my leg you can count the change in my pocket?
别担心，
Don't worry.
我想他会接受的 因为他也接受伊森这么做
He'd be okay with you because he's okay with Ethan.
伊森?有伊森这号人物?
Ethan? There's an Ethan?
伊森是我的男友
Ethan is my boyfriend.
什么?
What?
告诉我你期待我们之间会有什么关系...
What kind of relationship do you imagine us having...
既然你已有丈夫和男友
...if you have a husband and a boyfriend?
大概是性关系吧
I suppose,mainly sexual.
真是遗憾，你们散了
Sorry it didn't work out.
什么,散了? 周四我还要和她约会
What,not work out? I'm seeing her again on Thursday.
难道你没听懂?
Didn't you listen to the story?
Didn't you listen?
这太离谱了！你怎能和这种女人交往?
It's twisted!How could you get involved with her?
开始我也无法接受 但后来我想此事也挺好
I had trouble with it at first. But I get the good stuff.
只有谈天说笑和做爱...
All the fun,all the talking,all the sex...
不用负任何责任
...and none of the responsibility.
-这是每个男人的梦想 -是吗?未必吧
-This is every guy's fantasy! -That's not true!
-罗斯，这是你的梦想吗? -当然不是
-Ross,is this your fantasy? -No,of course not.
没错，是
Yeah. Yeah,it is.
你们男生不介意 和已有对象的女人交往?
You'd go out with someone going out with someone else?
-我办不到 -干得好，乔伊
-I couldn't. -Good for you.
和女人交往时,我必须确定...
When l' m with a woman,I need to know...
...我交往的对象比她多
... I' m going out with more people than her.
一次我和一个刚离婚的家伙出去
Once,I went out with a guy who just got divorced.
这很麻烦.相比之下 他的孩子更喜欢我一些
It was hard. His kids liked me better than him.
钱德必须作些什么呢?
What does this have to do with Chandler?
什么也不用.
Nothing.
关于这个话题我什么都不想说
I didn't have anything on that topic.
好吧，我换一种方法
So I went another way.
你知道,一夫一妻值得商榷
You know,monogamy can be a tricky concept.
就人类学的观点而言…
I mean,anthropologically speaking
好了…不听是你们的损失
Fine. Now you'll never know.
逗你的，告诉我们吧
We' re kidding. T ell us.
-我们想知道 -快说，
-We wanna know. -Come on!
好吧理查李奇提出这样的理论…
All right. There's a theory put forth by Richard Leakey
现在都这样打招呼吗?我喜欢
Are we greeting each other this way now? I like it.
瞧，我大扫除了
Look! I cleaned!
我擦窗户，拖地板
I did the windows. I did the floors.
我用了吸尘器上的所有功能除了那个圆形的之外,它有什么用处?
I used all the vacuum attachments but the round one. What's it for?
没人知道，我们也不该问
Nobody knows. And we're not supposed to ask.
你们感觉怎样?
What do you think?
-很干净 -真的看起来不错
-It's very clean. -Really,it looks great!
你移动了绿色的垫椅
I see you moved the green ottoman.
怎么会呢?
How did that happen?
我不知道,我以为摆那儿会更好看
I don't know. It looked better there.
咖啡桌旁就多了一个座位
And it's an extra seat around the table.
这倒有意思
Yeah,it's interesting.
这样好了，只是好玩...
But you know what? Just for fun...
...我们看它在原来位置的感觉如何
...Iet's see what it looked like in the old spot.
只是做个比较
Just to compare.
让我看看
Let's see.
放那儿也不错
Well,it looks good there too.
就摆那儿一阵子吧
Let's leave it there for a while.
我无法相信你竟敢搬动了绿色垫椅
I can't believe you moved the green ottoman.
幸好你没摊开杂志 否则她铁定会挖出你的眼睛
Be glad you didn't fan the magazines. She'll scratch your eyes out.
-各位，我没那么凶吧 -你就那么凶
-You guys,I am not that bad! -Yeah,you are.
记得我们住在一起时吗? 你就像个…
Remember,I lived with you? You were a little....
（电影《惊魂记》中杀人时的恐怖背景音乐）
这太不公平了
That is so unfair!
拜托，我们小时候 你连“破烂的安”（一种衣服破烂的布娃娃）都弄得一点都不破
When we were kids,yours was the only Raggedy Ann doll that wasn't raggedy.
我有责任感有组织性
Okay,so I'm responsible. I'm organized.
可是我也能很懒散
But hey,I can be a kook!
好吧，懒女人，
All right,you madcap gal!
想像这个情况
Imagine this.
电话单来 但你不立刻去交钱
The phone bill arrives,but you don't pay it right away.
-为什么? -因为你是个大懒人
-Why not? -Because you're a kook!
一直拖到他们寄催缴通知单来
You wait until they send a notice.
我可以办到
I could do that.
你让我去买日常用品
Okay,then you let me go grocery shopping
-没问题 -我还没说完
-No problem. -I'm not done yet.
我买了洗衣粉,但是是不容易倒出来的那种.
And I buy detergent,but it's not the one with the easy-pour spout.
有人会那样做吗?
Why would someone do that?
有人会想…
One might wonder.
我就没有问题
But I would be fine with that.
有人在咖啡桌上留下杯子 没有垫子,天气很热,一杯冷饮
A glass is on the table with no coaster. A cold drink. A hot day.
小水珠逐渐逼近桌面…
Beads of condensation are inching closer to the wood....
够了
Stop it!
天啊，
Oh,my God!
没错，我到底是谁?
It's true. Who am l?
莫妮卡，你是妈妈那样的.
Monica,you' re Mom.
天啊，
Oh,my God!
好，我会去的
Okay,I'll be there.
我的经纪人打来的
That was my agent.
他安排我在艾尔帕西诺的新片中演出
My agent has just gotten me a job in the new Al Pacino movie!
-太棒了… -演什么角色?
-That's great! -What's the part?
你们能相信吗?是艾尔帕西诺 我就是喜欢他才立志要当演员
Can you believe it? Pacino! This guy's why I became an actor!
"违反规程？你们违反规程！整个审判不合乎规程！"
（《伸张正义》中的台词）
" Out of order? You' re out of order! This whole courtroom's out of order! "
言归正传，什么角色?
Seriously,what's the part?
"当我认为已出局时 他们却又将我拉回"（《教父》中的台词）
"Just when I thought I was out,they pull me back in! "
快老实说，什么角色?
Come on. Seriously,Joey,what's the part?
你是…什么?
You' re.... What?
我是他臀部的替身
I' m his butt double,okay?
我演艾尔帕西诺的臀部
I play Al Pacino's butt.
他走进浴室,然后...
All right? He goes into the shower,and then...
...我就是他的屁股
... I' m his butt.
天呐
Oh,my God!
别这样
Come on,you guys.
这是一部艾尔帕西诺主演大制作的电影
It's a real Pacino movie and that's big!
别误会，这真是太棒了 这是你应得的
It's terrific. You deserve this.
这是你多年努力的成果 你终于能登上大银幕
After years of struggling you've cracked your way into show business.
行，笑吧，我不在乎
Fine. Make jokes,I don't care.
-这是我千载难逢的机会 -没错，
-This is a big break for me! -You' re right. It is.
你准备邀请我们参加你的首映会吗?
So,will you invite us to the big opening?
-我得向你借些保湿乳液 -干什么呢?
-I need some moisturizer. -For what?
今天可是我的大日子
T oday's the big day!
你有镊子吗?我的毛发太乱啦
You got any tweezers? I think I have a rogue hair.
好吧，进浴室要用什么自己拿
God. Go in the bathroom. Use whatever you want.
只是别告诉我你在里面干什么
Don't ever tell me what you did in there.
谢谢
Thank you.
-乔伊在哪儿?他妈打电话来 -他在浴室里，
-Joey's mom's on the phone. -ln the bathroom.
-你最好别进去 -拜托，我们是室友
-You don't wanna go in there! -Come on,we' re roommates.
我的眼睛!我的眼睛!
My eyes! My eyes!
我警告过你
I warned you.
谁在大吼大叫
Who is being loud?
一定是莫妮卡
Oh,that would be Monica.
我能借点东西吗? 我想为亚萝拉做早点
Can I borrow stuff? I wanna make Aurora breakfast.
她陪你一夜?
You got the whole night?
没错，我们只剩20分钟 直到伊森…
Well,I only have 20 minutes until Ethan,so....
难道我感到了怨恨?
Do I sense resentment?
不，没有怨恨，相信我……
No. No resentment. Believe me...
……绝对值得
...it's worth it,okay?
在你交往的过程中 有多少重要的时刻 会让你怀念一辈子?
In a relationship,you have moments you'll remember the rest of your life.
与亚萝拉相处的每一秒都是
Every single second is like that with Aurora.
而我已浪费35秒和你们说话
I've just wasted 35 of them talking to you.
莫妮卡请帮我开门
So,Monica,can you help me with the door?
钱德，老莫妮卡会提醒你
The old Monica would remind you...
……用塑胶刷刷特弗龙锅
...to scrub that T eflon pan with a plastic brush.
但我不会那么做的
But l' m not gonna do that.
不好意思?他们热身的怎么样了? 我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
Excuse me? Can they warm it up? I' m concerned about goose bumps.
大家准备好没?
Everybody ready?
我只是想感谢你给我这个机会
I wanna thank you for this opportunity.
我是说,我知道这只是第一步 但是我期待有一天
I mean,I know this is just a first step,but I hope that someday
解开浴袍
Lose the robe.
好，我正解开浴袍
Right. Okay. Losing the robe!
浴袍已解开
Okay,and the robe is lost.
各位，我想一次解决
I would like to get this in one take.
来吧，
Let's roll it.
放水
Water's working.
开始!
And action!
停!
And cut!
屁股男，你在干什么?
Butt guy,what are you doing?
我在洗澡
I'm showering.
不，你在挤屁股
No,that was clenching.
我认为他很沮丧
The way I see it,the guy's upset here,you know?
他的太太死了，弟弟失踪了
His wife's dead,his brother's missing.
我想他的屁股一定很愤怒
I think his butt would be angry here.
我想他的屁股会想在午餐前拍完
I think his butt would like to get the shot before lunch.
再来一次,开机 放水
Once again,rolling. Water working.
开始
And action!
停！你又在干什么?
And cut! What was that?
我要表现出绝望
I was going for quiet desperation.
如果你要求这样的话
But if you have to ask....
天啊，我爱这些手指
God,I love these fingers.
谢谢
Thank you.
不，我是指我的手指
No,actually,I meant my fingers.
你瞧它们多开心
Look at them. Look at how happy they are.
-天啊，我来不及了 -天啊,不
-Oh,my God,l' m late! -Oh,no!
-不要走 -好不好
-Don't go. -Okay.
-我得走了 -看,她走了
-I have to. -Look,she's leaving.
抱歉，他在等我了
I' m sorry. He'll be waiting for me.
-我以为你跟瑞克谈过 -不是瑞克
-I thought you talked to Rick. -It's not Rick.
是伊森?他要陪你一整天
Ethan? He gets the whole day!
不是他，是安德鲁
No,it's Andrew.
我知道……
I know there'll be moments...
……我会后悔问你这个问题，但是……
...when I'll regret asking the following question,but....
-这个安德鲁是……
-And Andrew is? -He's...
……新欢
... new.
你是说瑞克，伊森和我 三人还不能满足你?
So you' re not completely fulfilled by Rick,Ethan and myself?
我以前不是这种人
No,that's not exactly what I was
不知道多少女人……
Most women would kill...
……被我们三人迷倒
...for three guys like us.
-你想要什么? -你
-So,what do you want? -You.
-你已拥有我 -不，只是你
-You have me. -No. Just you.
-什么意思? -甩掉其他人
-What do you mean? -Lose the other guys.
他们全部?
Like,all of them?
我们这样不是很快乐吗?为什么不行?
Come on,we' re great together. Why not?
我们为何不能即时行乐?
Can't we have what we have now?
为何不能只是聊天,做爱……
Why can't we talk and make love...
……彼此没有任何负担?
...without feeling obligated to each other?
今晚之前,我以为这也是你想要的
Up until tonight,I thought that's what you wanted too.
部分是我想要的
Well,part of me wants that...
...但我就像是双面人 一个说“闭嘴,这样很好”
... but it's like l' m two guys. One guy's saying,"This is great! "
但是还有另一个
But there's this other guy.
当格林奇（童话人物，心脏只有别人的1/4大）的心长大
The guy who wells up when the Grinch's heart grows...
冲破了测量设备
...and breaks that measuring device.
他说“这太难了，快脱身”
He's saying,you know,"This is too hard. Get out! "
你听哪一个的话?
So,which one of the guys will you listen to?
两人的话我得都听 他们争执不休
I have to listen to both. They don't let each other finish.
哪一个？
Which one?
第二个
The second guy.
好吧，
I see.
改变主意后再打电话给我吧
Call me if you change your mind.
抱歉，是第一个动的口
Sorry,the first guy runs the lips.
这样想吧，你把她甩了
Look at it this way. You dumped her!
真的?我是说,这女人性感……
Right? I mean,this woman was unbelievably sexy...
……美丽聪明而且遥不可及
...and beautiful,intelligent,unattainable.
再告诉我一次,你为何这么做
Tell me why you did this again?
电影明星他回来了
Movie star!
等等，你不是在艾尔帕西诺新片中 演屁股的那个?
Wait! Aren't you the guy who plays the butt in the new Pacino movie?
不是
Nope.
不是?怎么了，大个儿?
No? What happened,big guy?
大个儿?
Big guy?
感觉就像“大个儿”时刻
It felt like a "big guy" moment.
我被开除了
I got fired!
他们说我太投入了
They said I acted too much with it.
我到处宣扬
I told everybody about this!
-现在大家都想到戏院看我演… -知道吗?
-Everybody's expecting to see me. -lKnow what?
-乔伊，没人会认出来的 -我妈就认得出来
-No one will be able to tell. -My mom will.
真是令人感动，又恶心
There's something so sweet and disturbing about that.
六年来我除了演些烂角色一事无成
I've done crappy plays for six years...
如今机会来了我竟将它搞砸
...and I finally get my shot,and I blow it!
等等，或许这不是你的机会
Maybe this wasn't it.
机会是否来临自己最清楚
I think when it's your shot,you know it's your shot.
你感觉这是你的机会吗?
Did it feel like your shot?
很难分辨，我当时全身赤裸
Hard to tell. I was naked.
我不认为这是你唯一的机会 你的机会不会只有一个
I don't think this was it. I don't think you just get one.
我相信大好机会就要降临到你身上
I believe things are gonna happen for you. I do.
你必须想着 将来有个小伙子跑到朋友面前说
You've got to think about the day some kid will go:
我被录取了… 我要演乔伊崔比亚尼的屁股
"l got the part! I'm gonna be Joey T ribbiani's ass! "
你真好
You think? That's so nice.
真遗憾，乔伊 各位，我要去睡了
I' m sorry,Joey. I' m gonna go to bed,guys.
-晚安 -晚安
-Good night. -Good night.
你要把鞋子留在这儿?
You' re gonna leave your shoes out here?
真的?就这样乱丢?
Really? Just casually strewn about...
...就这样轻率的,随意的乱扔?
...in that reckless,haphazard manner?
无所谓 我明天再拿,或者算了
It doesn't matter. I'll get them tomorrow. Or not!
随便
Whenever.
她真懒散
She is a kook.
既然这么困扰，就快去拿吧
If it bothers you that much,just go out and get the shoes.
不，千万别去
No,don 't do this!
太愚蠢了
This is stupid!
我无须证明什么，我要去拿
I don 't have to prove anything. I'm gonna get them.
但如此一来他们都会知道
But then everyone will know.
除非我去拿然后早起放回去
Unless I get them,then wake up really early and put them back.
谁来帮我一把!
I need help!
-你只是想要一个风铃 -不要唱这首歌
-All you want is a dinkle -Not that song!
-你讨厌流行的东西 -伙计们,不要这样
-All you envy's a schwang -Come on,you guys.
听它发出清脆的声音
A thing through which you can tinkle
拨弄着它，或是挂在那边
Or play with or simply let hang
你只是想要一个风铃
All you want is a dinkle
你讨厌流行的东西
What you envy's a schwang
听它发出清脆的声音
A thing through which you can tinkle
拨弄着它，或是挂在那边
Or play with or simply let hang